<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>

<content contentuid="h605cc54a-af27-4619-b0ac-3c1bf99e9356"  version="1">Wizard</content>
<content contentuid="hc9529073-7cb3-494e-bfae-ad3c5079b339"  version="1">You are an eldritch researcher and wizard. Your attire, a blend of scholarly black robes and occult symbols, reflects your unique path. With a furrowed brow, you pore over aged scrolls, deciphering cryptic incantations that speak of cosmic forces and forbidden knowledge. Your methodical approach to research combines traditional spellcraft with unorthodox experimentation, pushing the boundaries of magical understanding. The room hums with an eerie energy as you delve deeper into eldritch secrets, ready to confront the enigmatic forces that others dare not explore.</content>
<content contentuid="h99ba88cd-bea1-4042-88f5-9d99d738204e"  version="1">Eldritch Scholar: Infernals</content>
<content contentuid="h4246e92c-833e-42eb-9bc0-2c044ab9b4f6"  version="1">You've consciously chosen to immerse yourself in the intricate mechanics of Infernal pacts, spells, and invocations. Your research unfolds like an intricate dance with the very essence of the infernal realm, seamlessly blending the conventional art of spellcraft with the daring experimentation that borders on the unholy. With a relentless thirst for knowledge, you delve into the sinister intricacies of these dark contracts, dissecting the forbidden words and rituals that bind mortals to infernal entities. Your work stands as a testament to your courage and commitment, as you navigate the perilous terrain where forbidden knowledge and otherworldly power converge.</content>
<content contentuid="hfa37c540-9bd6-4bdc-9c72-023e9143c036"  version="1">Eldritch Impediment</content>
<content contentuid="h856b3afd-2881-4974-89c6-4eb103987e29"  version="1">Embracing the enigmatic and otherworldly essence of this eldritch power, you find that wielding it without a guiding patron proves challenging. Yet, you have meticulously devised methods to harness these spells, meticulously documented in your grimoire as if preparing for intricate invocation rituals. This unique approach comes at a cost, as you experience a -2 reduction in your Armor Class (AC), a -5 decrease in your Spell Save DC, and a -5 penalty to both Melee and Ranged spell attacks. However, these trials grant you access to newfound abilities: 'Deconstruction: Seeking Eldritch Magic' and 'Empowered Eldritch Magic.'</content>
<content contentuid="h6c84168b-237b-4365-94a9-5a007645f46c"  version="1">Eldritch Affinity: Initiate</content>
<content contentuid="h23725e02-c4ab-43e1-9bcc-7cb13cecaaf6"  version="1">Eldritch Affinity: Novice</content>
<content contentuid="h7fcfea1a-9b07-4371-8c58-6f903714421c"  version="1">Eldritch Affinity: Adept</content>
<content contentuid="hc9197a0d-5077-4951-8c86-bc69d57949bd"  version="1">Eldritch Affinity: Expert</content>
<content contentuid="hff483e79-c08c-452e-9403-8b1278b4ab36"  version="1">Eldritch Affinity: Master</content>
<content contentuid="he8eef05f-d949-46d2-bb3d-21a23f0d1adb"  version="1">As an initiate in the realm of eldritch magic, you are just beginning your journey into the mystical and enigmatic world of arcane forces. Your attire is plain, devoid of elaborate symbols or adornments, a reflection of your early exploration of this magical realm. Within your modest study, dimly lit by a few flickering candles, you delve into introductory grimoires and scrolls with a sense of wonder. Your brow furrows with concentration as you strive to decipher the cryptic incantations and symbols that hint at the profound mysteries of eldritch magic. You stand at the very beginning of your magical path, fueled by an insatiable curiosity, as you tentatively navigate the realms of enchantments, spells, and the arcane forces that beckon you into a world of infinite possibilities. Your journey is just starting, with the promise of discovery and growth awaiting you on this enchanting odyssey.You have unlocked an ability to perform an invocation ritual of your choosing every morning. Each invocation performed costs 1 hp and 1 experimentation point at this level, lasts until long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h49ac39f7-ba55-4226-b0dd-bbf08d2b9340"  version="1">As a novice in the realm of eldritch magic, you find yourself in the early stages of your mystical journey. Your attire is unassuming, with subtle symbols hinting at your budding connection to the arcane. Within your modest study, the soft glow of a few candles illuminates your workspace as you earnestly explore introductory grimoires and scrolls. Your brow furrows in concentration as you decipher the cryptic incantations and symbols, gradually unraveling the mysteries of eldritch magic. You stand at the threshold of your magical adventure, guided by a growing curiosity as you cautiously navigate the realms of enchantments, spells, and the enigmatic forces that beckon you further into the world of magic. Your path is marked by the promise of learning and growth, as you embark on this captivating journey into the arcane.You have unlocked an ability to perform more intricate invocation rituals of your choosing every morning. Each invocation performed costs 10hp and 1 experimentation point at this level, lasts until long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h0e7bb85b-7e7b-45a9-9699-a4673e765438"  version="1">As an adept in the realm of eldritch magic, you have made substantial progress on your mystical journey. Your attire is a testament to your expertise, adorned with intricate symbols that speak of your mastery over the arcane. In the absence of a dedicated study, you carry the knowledge within, your mind a well-organized repository of eldritch wisdom. With ease, you navigate complex grimoires and intricate scrolls, deciphering cryptic incantations and symbols that unveil the intricate tapestry of eldritch magic. Your path is one of mastery, where you command the realms of enchantments, spells, and the enigmatic forces with a seasoned expertise that sets you apart. Your journey continues to be marked by profound knowledge and the potential for even greater revelations as you delve deeper into the mysteries of the arcane.You have unlocked an ability to perform more advanced invocation rituals of your choosing every morning. Each invocation performed costs 20hp at this level and 1 experimentation point, lasts until long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h203a41eb-04da-4391-8dc7-f8d0e62bfb66"  version="1">As an expert in the realm of eldritch magic, your mastery over the arcane is awe-inspiring. Your attire is a testament to your expertise, adorned with intricate symbols that radiate the profound connection you hold with eldritch forces. Your study is a reflection of your mastery, a sanctuary of ancient tomes, scrolls, and mystical artifacts. With unparalleled ease, you navigate through the most complex grimoires, deciphering cryptic incantations and symbols that unveil the intricate web of eldritch magic. Your path is one of absolute mastery, where you wield the powers of enchantments, spells, and the enigmatic forces with a seasoned expertise that commands respect and admiration. Your journey continues to be marked by profound revelations and the unceasing pursuit of arcane wisdom, as you delve ever deeper into the mysteries of the eldritch, leaving an indelible mark on the annals of magic.You have unlocked an ability to perform more advanced invocation rituals of your choosing every morning. Each invocation performed costs 30hp at this level and 1 experimentation point, lasts until long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="hf527c299-ce19-4702-a6a3-2bee3b4d7237"  version="1">As a master in the realm of eldritch magic, you are an unparalleled authority in the arcane arts. Your attire is a living tapestry of intricate symbols, embodying the profound connection you share with eldritch forces. You no longer require a dedicated study; the arcane knowledge flows effortlessly within you, a wellspring of wisdom and power. You have long transcended the need for grimoires and scrolls, for the very essence of eldritch magic is etched into your consciousness. Your path is one of absolute mastery, where you effortlessly wield the most intricate enchantments, spells, and enigmatic forces with a profound expertise that commands reverence and admiration. Your journey is marked by profound revelations and the unceasing pursuit of arcane wisdom, as you continue to deepen your understanding of the eldritch, leaving an indelible legacy in the annals of magic that will endure for generations to come. You are a true master of the arcane, a beacon of knowledge and power in the realm of eldritch magic.You have unlocked an ability to perform the most powerful invocation rituals of your choosing every morning. Each invocation performed costs 40hp and 1 experimentation point at this level, lasts until long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h03536270-2836-4dc1-a337-340ec29b95be"  version="1">Invocation Rituals: Initiate</content>
<content contentuid="h0b86e130-7356-4075-85c2-7649c7cc5db3"  version="1">Invocation Rituals: Novice</content>
<content contentuid="h052dd5e4-4343-482d-bd97-fa746b981c9d"  version="1">Invocation Rituals: Adept</content>
<content contentuid="h59164737-9c58-4ae9-8b6e-d71b628963e8"  version="1">Invocation Rituals: Expert</content>
<content contentuid="h1a23cdf3-0c1b-40f9-9be8-5f2ea05dd51f"  version="1">Invocation Rituals: Master</content>
<content contentuid="hb1a18667-e23f-428c-b218-49b716bb1031"  version="1">Perform an approximation of Warlock invocations without a patron. Costs 1 Hp and 1 Invocation Point per cast.</content>
<content contentuid="h6d9c7be2-ee28-4fed-8e15-201bb5df207c"  version="1">Perform an approximation of Warlock invocations without a patron. Costs 1 0Hp and 1 Invocation Point per cast.</content>
<content contentuid="hbcdd5388-2e04-4583-816c-e12ef0d66abb"  version="1">Perform an approximation of Warlock invocations without a patron. Costs 20Hp and 1 Invocation Point per cast.</content>
<content contentuid="h8dc9386d-aeaf-496e-99aa-fd5511735be8"  version="1">Perform an approximation of Warlock invocations without a patron. Costs 30Hp and 1 Invocation Point per cast.</content>
<content contentuid="h3b8b0423-7d14-4fb2-b4a7-771037ef299c"  version="1">Perform an approximation of Warlock invocations without a patron. Costs 40 Hp and 1 Invocation Point per cast.</content>
<content contentuid="hee932a36-e8c2-4ea2-81b9-779621d44289"  version="1">Reading, observation, journaling, and experimentation</content>
<content contentuid="h45de94f2-cbbe-452b-9a65-201ce2cf3554"  version="1">Research: Conservative approach</content>
<content contentuid="hbd293551-6ac5-4762-8e34-0f78ff75799d"  version="1">Conservative research embodies a cautious and methodical approach to knowledge acquisition. It relies on established methodologies, meticulous documentation, and a steadfast commitment to tradition. Researchers who embrace this approach prioritize precision and accuracy, often proceeding with measured steps and due diligence. They are guardians of existing knowledge, preserving and refining what is already known before venturing into the unknown. This approach ensures a solid foundation upon which new discoveries can be built, emphasizing stability and reliability in the pursuit of understanding.You increase your AC by 1.</content>
<content contentuid="hbfbbb78f-a4df-4424-bdb6-aa4dfad1ff0e"  version="1">Conservative research embodies a cautious and methodical approach to knowledge acquisition. It relies on established methodologies, meticulous documentation, and a steadfast commitment to tradition. Researchers who embrace this approach prioritize precision and accuracy, often proceeding with measured steps and due diligence. They are guardians of existing knowledge, preserving and refining what is already known before venturing into the unknown. This approach ensures a solid foundation upon which new discoveries can be built, emphasizing stability and reliability in the pursuit of understanding.You increase your AC by 2.</content>
<content contentuid="h857f85a9-6446-4e0e-a91b-dc0a60a4f530"  version="1">Conservative research embodies a cautious and methodical approach to knowledge acquisition. It relies on established methodologies, meticulous documentation, and a steadfast commitment to tradition. Researchers who embrace this approach prioritize precision and accuracy, often proceeding with measured steps and due diligence. They are guardians of existing knowledge, preserving and refining what is already known before venturing into the unknown. This approach ensures a solid foundation upon which new discoveries can be built, emphasizing stability and reliability in the pursuit of understanding.You increase your AC by 3.</content>
<content contentuid="h61594959-a500-4353-8ac4-d88a690142df"  version="1">Research: Aggressive approach</content>
<content contentuid="h193b0caa-3f1d-4f12-b6d8-b3a834771854"  version="1">Aggressive research is a relentless pursuit of knowledge, driven by unwavering determination and a hunger for breakthroughs. It's the relentless exploration of uncharted territories, pushing the boundaries of what's known and accepted. Researchers employing this approach leave no stone unturned, embracing risks and challenges with a fearless spirit. Their passion fuels their tenacity, and they understand that sometimes, to unveil the most profound truths, one must be unapologetically relentless in the pursuit of answers.You can't have an omelete without breaking a few eggs, or so they say. You gain 2 extra experimentation points you can use to deconstruct spells, perform warlock invocations.</content>
<content contentuid="h9ccdf29f-473c-4541-a0de-a7b429badf5c"  version="1">Aggressive research is a relentless pursuit of knowledge, driven by unwavering determination and a hunger for breakthroughs. It's the relentless exploration of uncharted territories, pushing the boundaries of what's known and accepted. Researchers employing this approach leave no stone unturned, embracing risks and challenges with a fearless spirit. Their passion fuels their tenacity, and they understand that sometimes, to unveil the most profound truths, one must be unapologetically relentless in the pursuit of answers.You can't have an omelete without breaking a few eggs, or so they say. You gain 3 extra experimentation points you can use to deconstruct spells, perform warlock invocations.</content>
<content contentuid="hbb009fd4-b331-4f75-be10-7a67f1527c4b"  version="1">Aggressive research is a relentless pursuit of knowledge, driven by unwavering determination and a hunger for breakthroughs. It's the relentless exploration of uncharted territories, pushing the boundaries of what's known and accepted. Researchers employing this approach leave no stone unturned, embracing risks and challenges with a fearless spirit. Their passion fuels their tenacity, and they understand that sometimes, to unveil the most profound truths, one must be unapologetically relentless in the pursuit of answers.You can't have an omelete without breaking a few eggs, or so they say. You gain 4 extra experimentation points you can use to deconstruct spells, perform warlock invocations.</content>
<content contentuid="hd18e0757-8b0d-4ca7-8905-8179bcef762b"  version="1">Research Culmination</content>
<content contentuid="h2631f764-4ff9-4163-b4ca-e23850185af6"  version="1">Having completed your extensive research, you now possess a profound understanding of eldritch magic and its various forms. You've traversed the path less traveled and have emerged with a comprehensive grasp of its intricacies. The tantalizing scent of a potential breakthrough once hung in the air, but it has now materialized into a profound revelation. As you stand on the precipice of your game-changing discovery, it's not a question of how you'll chart the course of your research but how you'll harness the newfound knowledge of eldritch magic and its myriad forms. The world of arcane possibilities lies before you; how will you wield this newfound power for the betterment of your magical endeavors?</content>
<content contentuid="h489146df-644c-4429-aaf3-abf5dfa09b4b"  version="1">Thesis: Infernal Patrons</content>
<content contentuid="h99b69fbc-cd5c-4b36-b288-435cc6af9919"  version="1">The Unveiling of Infernal Patrons: A Comprehensive Study of Their Influence, Contracts, and Implications in Eldritch Magic</content>
<content contentuid="hc1b48124-3c01-4342-bd54-f935c33cc542"  version="1">Dissertation: Infernal Patrons</content>
<content contentuid="h4b12799a-e45c-4393-842d-685e58d7de2f"  version="1">Binding the Infernal Covenant: An In-Depth Exploration of Infernal Patrons and Their Pact-Making Dynamics in Eldritch Magic</content>
<content contentuid="h1709aefd-f52b-46e1-b5c6-3dfc2cf16914"  version="1">Book: Infernal Patrons</content>
<content contentuid="h4b95063a-ce84-40f2-b048-36eed763e30a"  version="1">Eldritch Grimoire: Unveiling the Dark Arts of Infernal Patrons, Warlocks, and the Secrets of Eldritch Magic</content>
<content contentuid="h126b16e6-d792-4ce6-bedd-b790fc8dd2f1"  version="1">Your spell gains advantage</content>
<content contentuid="hc20070fc-1d72-4e01-8798-6b4d09b78c01"  version="1">Deconstruction: Empowered Eldritch Magic</content>
<content contentuid="hd37a3ef1-b94f-4890-970d-3fe4744c52b7"  version="1">Experimentation Points</content>
<content contentuid="he2d5b4f7-8837-4a15-99d5-22f93c9edbb9"  version="1">Aggressive research is a relentless pursuit of knowledge, driven by unwavering determination and a hunger for breakthroughs. It's the relentless exploration of uncharted territories, pushing the boundaries of what's known and accepted. Researchers employing this approach leave no stone unturned, embracing risks and challenges with a fearless spirit. Their passion fuels their tenacity, and they understand that sometimes, to unveil the most profound truths, one must be unapologetically relentless in the pursuit of answers.You can't have an omelete without breaking a few eggs, or so they say. You gain 5 extra experimentation points you can use to deconstruct spells, perform warlock invocations.</content>
<content contentuid="h87bedfc0-5479-46a1-afc3-32fa1adca114"  version="1">Conservative research embodies a cautious and methodical approach to knowledge acquisition. It relies on established methodologies, meticulous documentation, and a steadfast commitment to tradition. Researchers who embrace this approach prioritize precision and accuracy, often proceeding with measured steps and due diligence. They are guardians of existing knowledge, preserving and refining what is already known before venturing into the unknown. This approach ensures a solid foundation upon which new discoveries can be built, emphasizing stability and reliability in the pursuit of understanding.You increase your AC by 4.</content>
<content contentuid="h65228e72-5b40-47fa-9f68-0d32f6333ce1"  version="1">Deconstruction: Seeking Eldritch Magic</content>
<content contentuid="h1b478ce8-b292-4b3f-9192-022a4e8d388f"  version="1">Your spell gains bonus damage</content>
<content contentuid="hbc97d004-c1d7-4974-952c-f68079f44e96"  version="1">Deconstruction: Agonizing Blast</content>
<content contentuid="h4dbd513b-ae5a-4f78-ba1d-293439031bfd"  version="1">Deconstruction: Armor Of Shadows</content>
<content contentuid="h873ee9e4-1621-4d17-97c9-cc4a969c1fae"  version="1">Deconstruction: Beast Speech</content>
<content contentuid="he727c99d-bdbb-4235-b829-f51c38580222"  version="1">Deconstruction: Beguiling Influence</content>
<content contentuid="hb329b9b8-deef-4836-a448-c0f8653331d9"  version="1">Deconstruction: Devils Sight</content>
<content contentuid="ha9f3099d-cac0-41ca-9e5c-da5a3935684b"  version="1">Deconstruction: Eldritch Mind</content>
<content contentuid="h05469f69-a6c2-4f14-99e5-c1b044066474"  version="1">Deconstruction: Eldritch Spear</content>
<content contentuid="h60f2d515-8c16-4264-8fcc-afff9324ff36"  version="1">Deconstruction: Fiendish Vigor</content>
<content contentuid="hf7c4fe63-78c0-4421-abe6-7aa610992d69"  version="1">Deconstruction: Grasp of Hadar</content>
<content contentuid="h9b766259-8851-4ff4-9153-0ce4d52e5c1a"  version="1">Deconstruction: Lance of Lethargy</content>
<content contentuid="h2363dbac-64ef-4842-9481-728dd381f64b"  version="1">Deconstruction: Mask Of Many Faces</content>
<content contentuid="h7bef8b65-69db-4fe4-90d0-4f20a96a39df"  version="1">Deconstruction: One With Shadows</content>
<content contentuid="h027aa4a6-e3ad-4cee-830e-94788e4e5c2d"  version="1">Deconstruction: Repelling Blast</content>
<content contentuid="hcdbb74ac-6721-44bd-a76f-8e6bbf1c0c01"  version="1">Deconstruction: Thief Of Five Fates</content>
<content contentuid="h0d16136f-9482-4533-a63d-624d7f073eba"  version="1">Deconstruction: Cloak of Flies</content>
<content contentuid="h600734c7-1664-4495-8da9-83ae83f12ebb"  version="1">Deconstruction: Eldritch Smite</content>
<content contentuid="h8db15c0d-abb0-4073-9bb5-421252e05b42"  version="1">Deconstruction: Mire The Mind</content>
<content contentuid="habc888ff-dcfd-4a28-bcb7-2665c9b3e08e"  version="1">Deconstruction: Sign Of Ill Omen</content>
<content contentuid="h79503ead-bc87-44ab-b549-0cf446cfdc1d"  version="1">Deconstruction: Tomb of Levistus</content>
<content contentuid="h406e514d-1dc6-4f27-a038-beea90cd1aff"  version="1">Deconstruction: Undying Servitude</content>
<content contentuid="hbb33dc5e-0672-4965-851d-88152c4447b6"  version="1">Deconstruction: Ghostly Gaze</content>
<content contentuid="hecb2be91-a474-4c90-a79c-92629d118199"  version="1">Deconstruction: Maddening Hex</content>
<content contentuid="ha143e495-bf24-4ce6-a3ad-dfdb689ed899"  version="1">Deconstruction: Book Of Ancient Secrets</content>
<content contentuid="hada57525-e419-421c-abf4-6ccb39d5aa73"  version="1">Deconstruction: Dreadful Word</content>
<content contentuid="h689329ed-14e9-43a4-bcf2-853e1e1e8db3"  version="1">Deconstruction: Sculptor Of Flesh</content>
<content contentuid="hcd389ea5-c222-42d0-a9de-b4a05b147f44"  version="1">Deconstruction: Relentless Hex</content>
<content contentuid="h9bc0f2a9-2966-410e-91ff-fc88332ec5ec"  version="1">Deconstruction: Improved Pact Weapon</content>
<content contentuid="hde825c0c-e4b1-43d4-a226-054c34ccfcdc"  version="1">Deconstruction: Minions Of Chaos</content>
<content contentuid="hb9948e84-030b-4690-9e39-37c79bf1f3c1"  version="1">Deconstruction: Otherworldly Leap</content>
<content contentuid="h7f5599bc-9e5c-49cc-ac71-9394c2adf74d"  version="1">Deconstruction: Whispers Of The Grave</content>
<content contentuid="h7f41046c-26f4-4020-b263-ca735187eed2"  version="1">Deconstruction: Tricksters Escape</content>
<content contentuid="h97555ac6-6ae2-441c-badc-011c70bebee4"  version="1">Deconstruction: Ascendant Step</content>
<content contentuid="h8daaaca4-60c1-44f0-8c73-001869e4fda7"  version="1">Gain Agonizing Blast, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="hcaa69713-f960-4f02-8aef-7a38b231e559"  version="1">Gain Armor Of Shadows, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h6550a868-a447-4147-8b44-ea0272b73f49"  version="1">Gain Ascendant Step, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h4d9eaf77-3542-4bda-ac92-10ab5398df5b"  version="1">Gain Beast Speech, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h0a3c75d9-4c18-4dcc-8197-61732d976ea4"  version="1">Gain Beguiling Influence, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h092a7029-ffe5-4267-ac4c-6d4e3fa9b525"  version="1">Gain Book Of Ancient Secrets, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h2c7cb143-e086-4240-b109-9de2447768d9"  version="1">Gain Cloak of Flies, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="hc822a9c5-71d5-4da0-aa2a-59b4e5769dc5"  version="1">Gain Devil's Sight, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h2f9bf25e-4a28-48c7-97cc-6233cd3525ba"  version="1">Gain Dreadful Word, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h47263f08-435a-4356-80d2-00f0b6e1f0ce"  version="1">Gain Eldritch Mind, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="he747563a-6472-48c9-8cc1-89a482ad0e94"  version="1">Gain Eldritch Smite, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h77bffd12-d2bb-4c33-9592-3a55dfe2b5a7"  version="1">Gain Eldritch Spear, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="hb2a5cdaa-ba46-4ebb-b74a-561d162fef68"  version="1">Gain Fiendish Vigor, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h73051d6b-be78-4f6e-8324-00241d46bacc"  version="1">Gain Ghostly Gaze, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h2a4a0a0e-8137-4a58-a257-000346a31581"  version="1">Gain Grasp of Hadar, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h8e544c05-3b2b-4f66-9bd7-a801a05a0cd3"  version="1">Gain Improved Pact Weapon, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h81f25139-1044-4544-b3d5-707fd3937656"  version="1">Gain Lance of Lethargy, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="hdf2c0404-846a-4b45-81ac-f8b8af427f2a"  version="1">Gain Maddening Hex, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="hae6d283b-29c3-4cc2-a475-c8744a11fec8"  version="1">Gain Mask Of Many Faces, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h2bf54623-de96-48dd-b233-8ce2719862c4"  version="1">Gain Minions Of Chaos, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="hc40ed6d8-138d-409c-84ec-b9f5dde2dada"  version="1">Gain Mire The Mind, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h15a77e0c-5b24-4036-8db2-4f824b108ab6"  version="1">Gain One With Shadows, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h6dc9614d-317f-4b1d-a8af-eb62c72cdf4a"  version="1">Gain Otherworldly Leap, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h0be649f6-8de2-49b9-936f-0b8b6adff804"  version="1">Gain Relentless Hex, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="hddfbcb90-9360-4493-8929-94a423facf70"  version="1">Gain Repelling Blast, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="hda4b9fce-a56d-48e2-8936-56a82a99bf49"  version="1">Gain Sculptor Of Flesh, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="hb622fe9c-c4f4-4d0a-9d92-c1a6fc8f633a"  version="1">Gain Sign Of Ill Omen, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h0d1d5c21-0691-45a5-ae4d-52c9cb236a59"  version="1">Gain Thief Of Five Fates, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h1431b248-b815-48f9-a357-f55e07199fb5"  version="1">Gain Tomb of Levistus, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h00f22897-9b2d-4713-8812-5eabf5141beb"  version="1">Gain Trickster's Escape, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="hdb579d79-add3-48d9-9dd1-e802642c745e"  version="1">Gain Undying Servitude, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="hc6f41aae-0787-4687-b7e4-ddc5b214bb15"  version="1">Gain Whispers Of The Grave, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="h7f6c897b-2f16-482f-8a5f-611faa9f8525"  version="1">Deconstruction: Lifedrinker</content>
<content contentuid="h63f1fbfe-021e-4652-b281-51e6d72d073d"  version="1">Gain Lifedrinker, an approximation of a warlock invocation at the cost of 1 experimentation point. This will remain active up until next long rest.</content>
<content contentuid="hcc0b91f0-a7f3-4343-8606-d1f4493891d9"  version="1">Despite your journey into a realm of magic far removed from the traditional studies of your peers, the underlying methods remain consistent. Theorycrafting and experimentation remain the tried-and-true means to grasp and unveil the enigmatic facets of this eldritch power. While others find comfort in established spells and familiar paths of magical learning, your research approach diverges onto a distinct road—one where innovation and adaptation become your steadfast companions.Your willingness to delve into the uncharted territories of magic brings a unique perspective to your studies. You find that by pushing the boundaries of your knowledge, you can uncover secrets that have eluded even the most seasoned mages. Your pursuit of this unconventional path not only deepens your understanding of the eldritch arts but also opens up avenues for creativity that others may never have imagined. How would you like to start your research?</content>
<content contentuid="hf41f699d-276e-4b6a-be99-7dfbcb7fe779"  version="1">Despite your journey into a realm of magic far removed from the traditional studies of your peers, the underlying methods remain consistent. Theorycrafting and experimentation remain the tried-and-true means to grasp and unveil the enigmatic facets of this eldritch power. While others find comfort in established spells and familiar paths of magical learning, your research approach diverges onto a distinct road—one where innovation and adaptation become your steadfast companions.You've made notable progress in your studies and have a basic understanding of the core concepts. With a bit more guidance, you could potentially make a significant discovery. How do you plan to continue your research from here?</content>
<content contentuid="h954b14da-d235-4029-b95a-8312463b2afb"  version="1">Despite your journey into a realm of magic far removed from the traditional studies of your peers, the underlying methods remain consistent. Theorycrafting and experimentation remain the tried-and-true means to grasp and unveil the enigmatic facets of this eldritch power. While others find comfort in established spells and familiar paths of magical learning, your research approach diverges onto a distinct road—one where innovation and adaptation become your steadfast companions.Your tireless efforts in this field have led to significant advancements, and you now possess a solid grasp of its fundamental principles. With the right guidance and a final push in the right direction, you stand on the brink of a potential breakthrough. How do you intend to navigate the path of your ongoing research?</content>
<content contentuid="h0d5c6a8e-0ec5-4a0c-8db4-1d06427b1272"  version="1">Despite your journey into a realm of magic far removed from the traditional studies of your peers, the underlying methods remain consistent. Theorycrafting and experimentation remain the tried-and-true means to grasp and unveil the enigmatic facets of this eldritch power. While others find comfort in established spells and familiar paths of magical learning, your research approach diverges onto a distinct road—one where innovation and adaptation become your steadfast companions.You've made significant strides in your studies and possess a firm grasp of the core concepts. The tantalizing scent of a potential breakthrough hangs in the air, just out of reach. With a little more guidance and perhaps a stroke of inspiration, you stand at the precipice of a potentially game-changing discovery. How will you chart the course of your research from this point onward?</content>
<content contentuid="h285db529-069a-4c89-9625-ea92cf842cde"  version="1">Binding Blade</content>
<content contentuid="h69305203-a24a-46f7-9d6a-0247e21cdd64"  version="1">You can &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="EW_Shout_PactOfTheBlade"&gt;Summon&lt;/LSTag&gt; a weapon, or &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="EW_Shout_PactOfTheBlade_Bind"&gt;Bind&lt;/LSTag&gt; the one you are wielding, making it magical</content>
<content contentuid="h9b3c9742-5fac-4fe5-b0b5-52e35b23146d"  version="1">Bound weapons use the wielder's &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellcastingAbilityModifier"&gt;Spellcasting Ability Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt; instead of &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Strength"&gt;Strength&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Dexterity"&gt;Dexterity&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
<content contentuid="hbf1822e1-9441-480f-bbcc-21e6cf7d5001"  version="1">You are &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficient&lt;/LSTag&gt; with the weapon. You can only have one at a time. The weapon disappears if you are more than [1] away from it for more than 10 rounds.</content>
<content contentuid="h9d07e52c-19b1-4ccd-b3f6-79aa1ab2b1c8"  version="1">Bind Weapon</content>
<content contentuid="h3389891d-80a8-4c80-ba22-1a9f25639000"  version="1">Bind to your main hand weapon. Its damage becomes magical, you cannot drop or throw it, and you become &lt;LSTag Tooltip="WeaponProficiency"&gt;Proficient&lt;/LSTag&gt; with it if you weren't already.</content>
<content contentuid="hd3ea4251-12d7-4244-abf1-fa78a8723e38"  version="1">Bind Rapier</content>
<content contentuid="h56b9dd60g52aeg487bgafe6g3792773877b2"  version="1">Safer Experimentation</content>
<content contentuid="h6765a90dge933g4179g8615g8a89b13e82cb"  version="1">Make experiments safe</content>
<content contentuid="h2c08ab8e-bbd2-4293-a834-1c69c7b0cd81"  version="1">Heal</content>
<content contentuid="h8acd82dd-e252-45d7-a3e4-b00556b2f81e"  version="1">HealDesc</content>
<content contentuid="h2b985ba7-a56e-4407-9418-f46896717ae5"  version="1">Heal2</content>
<content contentuid="h07fcc412-9695-41f1-948b-79fe51fe380f"  version="1">Heal2Desc</content>
<content contentuid="h71df44b5-2ef8-40e8-b6b3-23e7817b52f0"  version="1">Heal3</content>
<content contentuid="h59e83fc1-8388-4634-a67d-cdd43663d0ff"  version="1">Heal3Desc</content>
<content contentuid="hff322547-9aae-45e1-a28e-b138b95d8948"  version="1">Heal4</content>
<content contentuid="h499a312d-2f42-4fad-b55b-703dbb6806ef"  version="1">Heal4Desc</content>
<content contentuid="h61a0c3ec-facb-414b-b753-39035be8a9db"  version="1">Harm</content>
<content contentuid="h14c25914-68bd-470a-ab98-1acd06b04626"  version="1">HarmDesc</content>
<content contentuid="hd0a84266-61db-43fd-a41f-f4a68f1fe0ff"  version="1">Harm2</content>
<content contentuid="h54f3d854-531f-40fc-bd60-536864f50676"  version="1">HarmDesc2</content>
<content contentuid="h2d584b01-fdac-4a87-8570-aea2e6d8903e"  version="1">Harm3</content>
<content contentuid="hbbdfb68b-c417-495b-b75b-f7b322ade88e"  version="1">HarmDesc3</content>
<content contentuid="h9b07d9b9-cc46-4394-81c2-a8f4f9d9cac4"  version="1">Harm4</content>
<content contentuid="hb2dd9ee2-bbe2-455f-95dd-b631cc74b2d2"  version="1">HarmDesc4</content>
<content contentuid="hf0ab5bb2-3a6f-4c1a-bd06-df85ec0c6968"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="hdc32aaad-9aa1-4480-ac0e-264075d8aec9"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="h3d1c8f09-32c3-4759-b029-986673b4d12a"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="hd0d12c7b-c7af-41af-b35a-c2fa7a453bb1"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="hf154a477-86d2-46c6-8b5a-c7eb02a77170"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="hb8f8c65b-bd16-4dd1-aed7-61583a37aff7"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="hed7464a2-69ee-4763-9999-409937412d1c"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="hea8858a9-3a1c-471c-8021-552e3d1ef808"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="h82fbfddd-ef6a-4d6b-a8d2-b06889486cab"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="ha84176d6-2525-48f6-b687-add8b7358562"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="h5af6853f-b706-408f-ae00-320cac5027dc"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="he00489d2-28c2-47aa-a3aa-56e393bcf2d3"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="ha37d0371-1edb-4de3-9b2e-d2781db4d12f"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="hb88afd9a-c996-43cc-97a3-0e67bfb3823f"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="hce0d5444-1723-410e-8ef5-6efc21ef1519"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="h69aa2f70-3618-42da-bc39-3d9de3a3542c"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="h68d065c0-7e20-460f-8305-27680dbe43bf"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="h35235d39-0214-4808-baf1-3d9e2409adb4"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="h33d73ca6-075f-42d7-82a9-49b6c410dae2"  version="1"></content>
<content contentuid="h7d18b947-081c-4980-b8c7-210977afb995"  version="1"></content>




</contentList>